[{"answer": "They do say the --", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 6, "question": "What are you two talking about?", "qSentId": 5}, {"answer": "The countdown really is beginning now.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What's happening?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I suspect that was quite an emotional journey.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "The bride is on the move to the palace?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "You know, this is expected earlier in the week, that three of the rooms in the palace are going to be transformed into a nightclub.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "What she's doing with disco balls?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "It's going to be a big party.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "And if Prince Harry's in charge of the party, it's going to be a big party, right?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, as it turns out, you can divorce anybody in the royal family and it will be OK, which we've kind of established ever since Henry VIII up through the present day.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "How important is it, do you think, constitutionally that William and Kate stay together?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "It's because you're in the star system and you're in the star system.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "It's not as sexy, is it, as a monarch monarchy, where no one can get rid of them?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "It's absurd.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "That it has to be the oldest boy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I think it's too early to say is the first point I'd make.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's inevitable with any world event -- and this is a world event now -- security has to be paramount.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What do you feel about the security?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I think she'll be hoping that they're happy fundamentally.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What do you think she'll be hoping from this wedding?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "I think she'd have been tremendously proud.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What do you think she would have made of all this?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I think it would have been really tough for her, this year in particular.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "How would she have coped psychologically do you think with William finding a rival love in many ways?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "She was amusing.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "What was she really like?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I worry a little but I think Kate has sorted it out.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Did you worry about Kate Middleton?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, yes, it tells you a lot about his weakness.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "It's hard to harangue a man who was forced through duty to marry the woman who wasn't really the love of his life, isn't it?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I don't find it as exciting as 1981.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "ORGAN: As we prepare for the big day, how does it feel for you compared to 1981?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I didn't have contact with William, unlike you.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Do you still have any contact with William?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "That's all it is, 300.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Oh, is that all?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "For the dinner, yes.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "For the dinner?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, it will be enormous.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "What will the pressure be like on the chefs for this one?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Well, think you've got to keep your British.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What would you -- what would you come up with?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "HITE: Gulls eggs.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Gulls eggs?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Really rich.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Are they very rich?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "You got to go for Eton Mess.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "And a pudding?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "It's very simple.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "What is an Eton Mess?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "It's -- well, one, I have an Italian mother.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "What does it mean to you to be British?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I think it brings out the best in people and reminds them of the great country that they've been brought up in and all those values.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What are the values you think -- when we have a royal wedding, when the world looks at us, what are the values that still remain quintessentially British?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Do you know what, not just a great day.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "I think it's going to be a great day, Friday, isn't it?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Sitting next to Sharon Osbourne in the rival box.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "In your pub?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I know some things.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Oh, you know that?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I think so, yeah.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Are you a romantic man?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I don't -- I guess if that's the definition of romantic, than maybe I'm not romantic.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "So when the big moment comes, when they come out on the balcony and they prepare for what we imagine will be the most viewed kiss in history, will you be feeling a little warm and cuddly inside?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I'll be on stage that night.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "You're going to be watching?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Seven thirty.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What time are you on?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "It's very good.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "How are you finding British beer, because we believe it's the best in the world?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "You into real ale, into a hand pumped real foaming bitter?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Oh yes.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Have you spoken to her majesty, the queen, in the build up to the wedding?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "You just did.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Can I use that word on this show?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "No, they know I'm trustworthy.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Do the British royals curtsy to you when they see you?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "No, I'm not, really.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Are you as excited about the wedding, as everybody else seems to be?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I think you can.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Can I say this on CNN?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, it's been going on and on and on.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "She is beautiful.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "What do you think of both William, our future king, and his choice of bride?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "I think she is .", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I was around.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "When Charles married Diana, where were you then?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "He liked me.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Did you ever things could have panned out differently?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, she calls me quite a lot.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Have you spoken to her majesty, the queen, in the build- up to the weddings?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "Yes, I bought them -- I thought of all the gifts that people from other nations will be giving them.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Have you got a gift for the royal couple?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Grill.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Grill?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "A fat free grill.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "One of those fat free grills?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "I didn't know that.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Did you know that?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "I heard speculation that you may have taken the seat that was originally reserved for Sarah, Duchess of York, for Fergie.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Are there Scrabble players watching?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Look, I am a royalist, viewers.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 712, "question": "Are you fans of theirs?", "qSentId": 711}, {"answer": "Look, they have withstood the media pressure.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "What advice do you give to the other royals about how to sustain the terrible media pressure you have had to withstand?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Larry King?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "He said you could be wife number nine, if you play your cards right.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "He's still alive?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Well, the word commoner doesn't mean much to Australians, and certainly not to Americans.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "How do you feel about our future king of England marrying a commoner?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "There are some people you and I would be very, very heavy to behead.", "docId": "110427pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "Would you allow the monarchs to behead people they didn't like, wives, husbands, that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 762}]